pubsns.com 2018-05-26

# 

Protecting your private information is our priority. This Statement of Privacy applies to the www.pubsns.com and governs data collection and usage. For the purposes of this Privacy Policy, unless otherwise noted, all references to pubsns.com. The pubsns website operates as an Affiliate Network Provider. By using the pubsns website, you consent to the data practices described in this statement. 

Collection of your Personal Information 

Pubsns may collect personally identifiable information, such as your name. We may gather additional personal or non-personal information in the future. Information about your computer hardware and software may be automatically collected by pubsns. 

This information can include: your IP address, browser type, domain names, access times and referring website addresses. This information is used for the operation of the service, to maintain quality of the service, and to provide general statistics regarding use of the pubsns website. 

Please keep in mind that if you directly disclose personally identifiable information or personally sensitive data through pubsns's public message boards, this information may be collected and used by others. pubsns encourages you to review the privacy statements of websites you choose to link to from pubsns so that you can understand how those websites collect, use and share your information. pubsns is not responsible for the privacy statements or other content on websites outside of the pubsns website. 

Use of your Personal Information 

Pubsns collects and uses your personal information to operate its website(s) and deliver the services you have requested. 

Pubsns may also use your personally identifiable information to inform you of other products or services available from pubsns and its affiliates. Pubsns may also contact you via surveys to conduct research about your opinion of current services or of potential new services that may be offered. pubsns does not sell, rent or lease its customer lists to third parties. pubsns may share data with trusted partners to help perform statistical analysis, send you email or postal mail, provide customer support, or arrange for deliveries. All such third parties are prohibited from using your personal information except to provide these services to pubsns, and they are required to maintain the confidentiality of your information. 

Pubsns will disclose your personal information, without notice, only if required to do so by law or in the good faith belief that such action is necessary to: (a) conform to the edicts of the law or comply with legal process served on pubsns or the site; (b) protect and defend the rights or property of pubsns; and, (c) act under exigent circumstances to protect the personal safety of users of pubsns, or the public. 

Use of Cookies 

The pubsns website may use "cookies" to help you personalize your online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hard disk by a web page server. Cookies cannot be used to run programs or deliver viruses to your computer. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. 

One of the primary purposes of cookies is to provide a convenience feature to save you time. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page. For example, if you personalize pubsns pages, or register with pubsns site or services, a cookie helps pubsns to recall your specific information on subsequent visits. This simplifies the process of recording your personal information, such as billing addresses, shipping addresses, and so on. When you return to the same pubsns website, the information you previously provided can be retrieved, so you can easily use the pubsns features that you customized. 

You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of the pubsns services or websites you visit. 

Security of your Personal Information 

Pubsns secures your personal information from unauthorized access, use or disclosure. When personal information (such as a credit card number) is transmitted to other websites, it is protected through the use of encryption, such as the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. 

Children Under Thirteen 

Pubsns does not knowingly collect personally identifiable information from children under the age of thirteen. If you are under the age of thirteen, you must ask your parent or guardian for permission to use this website. 

Opt-Out & Unsubscribe 

We respect your privacy and give you an opportunity to opt-out of receiving announcements of certain information. Users may opt-out of receiving any or all communications from pubsns by contacting us. Changes to this Statement pubsns will occasionally update this Statement of Privacy to reflect company and customer feedback. pubsns encourages you to periodically review this Statement to be informed of how pubsns is protecting your information. Contact Information pubsns welcomes your questions or comments regarding this Statement of Privacy. If you believe that pubsns has not adhered to this Statement, please contact contact@pubsns.com.
